Raymond, Eleanor. The Eleanor Raymond Collection: An Inventory.
Eleanor Raymond Collection.
- Series E / Eleanor Raymond Addendum, E000
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), : E021; / Quantity: 2 / Medium: film
Sketches / A2912, A333, A343, A3515, A3516, A3517, A3518, A3522, A353, A359, A3610, A3611, A364, A365, A3715, A3717, A372, A376, A378, A384, A386, A387, A389, A395, A398, A4013, A4014, A4017, A4018, A407, A412, A417, A4210, A424, A4311, A4412, A442, A444, A446, A449, A4511, A4512, A4517, A4518, A4522, A453, A4530, A456, A458, A4602, A4605, A4611, A4614, A4615, A4616, A4617, A4618, A4620, A4621, A4623, A4627, A4629, A4702, A4708, A4710, A4711, A4714, A4717, A4719, A4720, A4802, A4805, A4806, A4809, A4811, A4813, A4814, A4817, A4902, A4903, A4908, A4911, A4914, A4918, A4919, A4920, A4921, A5002, A5010, A5013, A5014, A5015, A5018, A5019, A5101, A5102, A5105, A5106, A5107, A5108, A5109, A5111, A5114, A5115, A5116, A5205, A5210, A5216, A5218, A5301, A5302, A5304, A5309, A5310, A5314, A5325, A5403, A5404, A5405, A5409, A5412, A5416, A5417, A5418, A5503, A5507, A5510, A5515, A5518, A5519, A5520, A5601, A5605, A5606, A5607, A5608, A5610, A5612, A5613, A5616, A5617, A5618, A5701, A5702, A5703, A5704, A5705, A5706, A5707, A5709, A5710, A5711, A5712, A5714, A5801, A5802, A5803, A5804, A5805, A5806, A5810, A5811, A5812, A5813, A5814, A5901, A5902, A5903, A5904, A5906, A5907, A5908, A5909, A5910, A5911, A5912, A5914, A5915, A5916, A5917, A5918, A5922, A5923, A5924, A5925, A5926, A6001, A6003, A6004, A6005, A6006, A6007, A6101, A6104, A6105, A6106, A6107, A6108, A6109, A6110, A6111, A6112, A6113, A6202, A6204, A6205, A6206, A6208, A6213, A6214, A6301, A6302, A6304, A6305, A6306, A6307, A6308, A6310, A6311, A6312, A6401, A6402, A6403, A6404, A6405, A6406, A6408, A6409, A6410, A6501, A6502, A6503, A6505, A6506, A6507, A6508, A6510, A6511, A6512, A6513, A6515, A6603, A6604, A6605, A6606, A6608, A6609, A6701, A6704, A6706, A6708, A6709, A6710, A6712, A6801, A6803, A6804, A6806, A6807, A6808, A6810, A6812, A6901, A6902, A6903, A6904, A7001, A7002, A7003, A7004, A7005, A7006, A7007, A7010, A7011, A7012, A7101, A7102, A7103, A7104, A7205, A7206, A7207, A7208, A7209, A7303, A7304, A7306, A7308, A7309, A7401, A7503
Slides / E012, E013, E014, E015, E016, E017, E018, E019, E020
Specification notes / A333, A386, A4522, A4605, A4704, A4805, A5010, A5014, A5018, A5019, A5101, A5108, A5205, A5301, A5302, A5310, A5409, A5505, A5507, A5510, A5517, A5520, A5605, A5608, A5614, A5704, A5707, A5710, A5801, A5802, A5805, A5904, A5912, A5916, A5918, A5922, A5923, A5925, A5926, A6004, A6005, A6105, A6106, A6109, A6112, A6113, A6205, A6302, A6304, A6305, A6307, A6310, A6311, A6312, A6401, A6406, A6408, A6501, A6502, A6506, A6508, A6511, A6513, A6603, A6606, A6608, A6701, A6703, A6704, A6706, A6709, A6710, A6711, A6803, A6804, A6806, A6807, A6808, A6810, A6812, A6901, A6902, A6903, A7002, A7003, A7005, A7101, A7102, A7202, A7205, A7302, A7401
Specifications / A3311, A333, A343, A3511, A3517, A3518, A3715, A376, A377, A398, A404, A416, A4522, A4605, A4621, A4629, A4712, A4719, A4802, A4907, A4919, A5002, A5010, A5101, A5103, A5301, A5309, A5310, A5515, A5601, A5605, A5613, A5614, A5616, A5617, A5810, A5812, A5912, A5915, A5917, A5921, A5924, A6101, A6106, A6113, A6403, A6404, A6410, A6701, A7206
Submittals / A5301
Supplements / A5924
Survey plans / A2912, A3511, A353, A3611, A376, A377, A398, A4602, A5304, A5310, A5409, A5416, A5614, A5616, A5710, A5711, A5916, A6104, A6106, A6312, A6402, A7102, A7204, A7305
Time cards / A7101, A7303, A7503
AAT Terms Index
Additions / Addenda A5917
Additions / Appeals A6502, A6803
Additions / Bids A6101
Additions / Blueprints A4918, A5015
Additions / Brochures A6810
Additions / Building programs A7403
Additions / Clippings A5613, A6003
Additions / Construction drawings A3610, A3715, A4621, A4814, A6511, A6901, A6902, A7207
Additions / Contracts A5505, A5704
Additions / Correspondence A5302, A5703, A5901, A6103, A6205, A6509, A6603, A6709, A6807, A6808
Additions / Design development drawings A5105, A5109, A5205, A5301, A5403, A7102
Additions / Diazo process prints A5216
Additions / Invoices A7103
Additions / Measured drawings A4410
Additions / Photographs A5518
Additions / Project files A4210, A5304
Alterations / Bids A6101
Alterations / Blueprints A4919, A5706
Alterations / Brochures A6810
Alterations / Clippings A5613, A6003
Alterations / Construction drawings A4629, A6311, A6408, A6410, A6601, A6902
Alterations / Contracts A5409, A5704, A6305, A6403, A6703
Alterations / Correspondence A5608, A5610, A5612, A5707, A5709, A5804, A5805, A5813, A5921, A5922, A5923, A6004, A6102, A6103, A6105, A6108, A6111, A6112, A6205, A6214, A6307, A6309, A6310, A6409, A6506, A6507, A6513, A6608, A6701, A6704, A6706, A6709, A6804, A6806, A6807, A6808, A6812, A7002, A7004, A7006
Alterations / Cuts A7302, A7304, A7503
Alterations / Design development drawings A5010, A5111, A5403, A5607, A7101, A7401
Alterations / Diazo process prints A5216, A6301, A6306, A6605, A7209, A7502
Alterations / Invoices A6505, A7307
Alterations / Measured drawings A5013, A5018, A7501
Alterations / Negatives A7104
Alterations / Notes A6708
Alterations / Project files A4702, A4720, A4806, A4813, A4907, A4914, A5115, A5304, A5404, A5519, A5605
Antique stores / Correspondence A7005
Apartments / Blueprints A456
Apartments / Clippings A5802
Apartments / Construction drawings A389
Apartments / Correspondence A5814, A5905, A6001, A6108, A6109, A6110, A6310
Apartments / Cuts A7304, A7308
Apartments / Design development drawings A5105, A5109, A5301
Apartments / Diazo process prints A5314, A5503
Apartments / Measured drawings A5412
Apartments / Project files A5902, A6006
Arbors / Correspondence A6208
Barns / Correspondence A5814, A6109
Barns / Cuts A7304
Barns / Project files A407, A6006
Built-in furniture / Blueprints A4616, A7008
Built-in furniture / Construction drawings A398, A6410, A6901, A7001, A7205, A7306
Built-in furniture / Contracts A6305
Built-in furniture / Correspondence A6302, A6308, A6507, A6804, A6806, A7002
Built-in furniture / Design development drawings A4605, A7101
Built-in furniture / Details A7011
Built-in furniture / Diazo process prints A5418
Built-in furniture / Invoices A5915
Built-in furniture / Project files A4612, A4615
Cabins / Project files A378
Chapels / Correspondence A5925
Churches / Photostats A5309
Closets / Clippings A5613
Clubhouses / Project files A387
Community centers / Correspondence A6007
Contractors / Blueprints A4919
Contractors / Clippings A5606
Contractors / Construction drawings A3715, A5614
Contractors / Contracts A5510
Contractors / Correspondence A5302, A5608
Contractors / Details A5507, A5517
Contractors / Measured drawings A4512, A4522
Cottages / Blueprints A5015
Cottages / Measured drawings A449, A5412
Country clubs / Correspondence A5904
Diazo process prints / Correspondence A6214
Electrical systems / Blueprints A4911
Electrical systems / Clippings A5613
Electrical systems / Construction drawings A376, A5601, A5614, A5616
Electrical systems / Correspondence A5608, A5912, A6113, A6701
Equipment / Addenda A5917
Exhibitions / Correspondence A6712
Exhibitions / Project files A5106
Experimental buildings / Blueprints A4921
Experimental buildings / Construction drawings A404, A416
Experimental buildings / Diazo process prints A5210
Experimental buildings / Plot plans A5218
Factories / Addenda A5917
Family compounds / Blueprints A4704
Family compounds / Construction drawings A419
Furniture / Addenda A5917
Furniture / Construction drawings A6710
Furniture / Correspondence A6107
Furniture / Details A5517
Furniture / Project files A5114
Garages / Appeals A6803
Garages / Blueprints A5015
Garages / Correspondence A6007, A6110, A6204
Garages / Design development drawings A5403, A7101
Garages / Project files A5102
Gardens / Clippings A6206
Gardens / Construction drawings A364, A3715
Gardens / Contracts A5101
Gardens / Correspondence A5805, A5908, A5910, A5919, A6208, A6212, A6506, A6711
Gardens / Design development drawings A424, A5010, A5107, A5301, A7101
Gardens / Diazo process prints A5216
Gardens / Measured drawings A5013
Gardens / Project files A4611, A4920
Greenhouses / Bids A6101
Greenhouses / Construction drawings A359
Greenhouses / Correspondence A6506
Hardware / Clippings A5613, A6106
Hardware / Construction drawings A333, A5614, A5616, A5812
Hardware / Contracts A5704
Hardware / Correspondence A5608, A5912
Hardware / Design development drawings A5310
Housing developments / Correspondence A5803
Housing projects / Construction drawings A395
Information centers / Correspondence A5909
Inns / Project files A4627, A4710
Interiors / Construction drawings A6410
Interiors / Contracts A6305, A6703
Interiors / Correspondence A5921, A6112, A6214, A6308, A6704, A6812
Interiors / Cuts A7503
Interiors / Design development drawings A454, A4902
Interiors / Diazo process prints A6301, A7502
Interiors / Interior perspectives A453
Interiors / Measured drawings A4610
Interiors / Project files A5618, A5907
Iron railings / Correspondence A6515
Kitchens / Blueprints A4918
Kitchens / Clippings A5613, A5926
Kitchens / Construction drawings A6311, A6511, A7003, A7205
Kitchens / Contracts A5409, A5510, A6305, A6403
Kitchens / Correspondence A5610, A5617, A5709, A5804, A5806, A5811, A5903, A6004, A6103, A6307, A6309, A6701
Kitchens / Design development drawings A4717, A5111, A7401
Kitchens / Details A5507
Kitchens / Diazo process prints A4711, A7209
Kitchens / Invoices A6503, A6505
Kitchens / Measured drawings A7501
Kitchens / Project files A4530, A5325
Lighting, architectural and decorative / Correspondence A6113
Masonry / Construction drawings A398
Meeting houses / Correspondence A5108
Memorials / Correspondence A6512, A6702
Notes / Correspondence A6309
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Blueprints A4918
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Clippings A5810
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Correspondence A6506
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Cuts A7308
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Design development drawings A4902
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Diazo process prints A5503
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Measured drawings A4514
Offices (rooms and spaces) / Project files A4620
Outbuildings / Blueprints A4714, A5015
Outbuildings / Construction drawings A343, A3516, A392
Outbuildings / Correspondence A6514
Outbuildings / Cuts A7304
Outbuildings / Design development drawings A5109
Outbuildings / Diazo process prints A4903, A5314
Outbuildings / Plot plans A5218
Outbuildings / Project files A372, A4708, A4811
Outdoor furniture / Correspondence A6512
Parking lots / Bids A5916
Plant materials / Clippings A6206
Plant materials / Correspondence A5924, A6506
Plant materials / Invoices A5915
Plaques / Correspondence A6515
Plaster / Construction drawings A376
Porches / Construction drawings A6901, A6902
Porches / Correspondence A6704, A6709
Porches / Diazo process prints A7209
Prefabricated buildings / Brochures A7206
Prefabricated buildings / Project files A6402
Preservation / Design development drawings A7102
Prototype buildings / Blueprints A4921
Prototype buildings / Brochures A7206
Prototype buildings / Project files A4618
Radio stations / Blueprints A4908
Railroad transportation buildings / Cuts A7308
Reconstructed sites / Clippings A5606
Rehabilitation centers / Correspondence A5108
Religious buildings / Bids A5916
Religious buildings / Blueprints A5515
Religious buildings / Clippings A5810
Religious buildings / Correspondence A5925, A6515
Religious buildings / Photographs C001
Remodeling / Bids A5916
Remodeling / Blueprints A4017, A447, A4908, A5103
Remodeling / Clippings A5926
Remodeling / Construction drawings A7003, A7205
Remodeling / Correspondence A5806, A5811, A5814, A5903, A5904, A5905, A5909, A6007, A6404
Remodeling / Design development drawings A424, A5010, A5417
Remodeling / Diazo process prints A5418, A5503
Remodeling / Invoices A6503
Remodeling / Project files A384, A444, A458, A5102, A5325
Renovations / Blueline prints A4517
Renovations / Blueprints A4518, A4602, A4614, A4719
Renovations / Clippings A5606, A5802, A5810
Renovations / Construction drawings A2912, A3515, A3611
Renovations / Contracts A5505, A5510
Renovations / Correspondence A5617, A6001, A6007, A6109, A6110, A7005
Renovations / Cuts A7308
Renovations / Design development drawings A4817, A4902
Renovations / Details A5507
Renovations / Measured drawings A4512, A4528
Renovations / Project files A417, A442, A4617, A4623, A5902, A6006
Renovations / Sketches A412
Single-family dwellings / Bids A6312
Single-family dwellings / Blueline prints A4805
Single-family dwellings / Blueprints A386, A4911, A5014, A5706
Single-family dwellings / Brochures A7206, A7303
Single-family dwellings / Building codes A6606
Single-family dwellings / Clippings A5705, A6005, A6104, A6106
Single-family dwellings / Construction drawings A2912, A3511, A3517, A3522, A364, A365, A3717, A376, A377, A398, A4412, A4511, A4712, A4809, A4814, A5116, A5601, A5616, A6401, A6406, A6710, A6903
Single-family dwellings / Contracts A5101, A5918, A6813
Single-family dwellings / Correspondence A5711, A5714, A5901, A5906, A5912, A5914, A5922, A5924, A6102, A6113, A6213, A6304, A6509, A6510
Single-family dwellings / Diazo process prints A304, A4903, A5210
Single-family dwellings / Invoices A5915, A7007, A7305
Single-family dwellings / Measured drawings A5416
Single-family dwellings / Negatives A4414
Single-family dwellings / Notes A5019, A6708
Single-family dwellings / Outline specifications A3518
Single-family dwellings / Photographs A275
Single-family dwellings / Project files A4018, A4311, A446, A4907, A5115, A5405, A6402
Single-family dwellings / Renderings C013
Solariums / Appeals A6502
Solariums / Bids A6101
Solariums / Construction drawings A6902
Solariums / Contracts A6703
Solariums / Correspondence A6205, A6701, A6706, A6807
Solariums / Photographs A5518
Speculative buildings / Invoices A7007
Stairways / Diazo process prints A7502
Stores / Correspondence A7005
Studies (rooms and spaces) / Correspondence A6302, A6405
Studies (rooms and spaces) / Measured drawings A7501
Studios / Construction drawings A333
Studios / Diazo process prints A4903
Studios / Project files A5701, A6006
Subdivisions / Correspondence A5803
Summer houses / Construction drawings A4715
Summer houses / Correspondence A5712
Swimming pools / Measured drawings A5416
Terraces / Correspondence A6208, A6506, A6801
Textiles / Addenda A5917
Town houses (urban dwellings) / Clippings A5802
Town houses (urban dwellings) / Correspondence A5921, A6001, A6310, A6804, A7006
Town houses (urban dwellings) / Design development drawings A5105
Town houses (urban dwellings) / Project files A5902
Unexecuted designs / Brochures A7303
Unexecuted designs / Clippings A5705, A6104
Unexecuted designs / Contracts A5918
Unexecuted designs / Correspondence A5707, A5711, A5712, A5714, A5803, A5813, A5906, A5914, A6001, A6105, A6213, A6304, A6310, A6510, A6608
Unexecuted designs / Cuts A7308
Unexecuted designs / Invoices A5915, A7103
Unexecuted designs / Negatives A7104
Unexecuted designs / Notes A5019
Unexecuted designs / Project files A5405, A7009
Workshops / Blueprints A4014
Workshops / Construction drawings A4013
Workshops / Correspondence A6807